Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel PAP. Today we are going to
talk about a great stock of ICL Group,
which is less in general discussion
but is a multibagger stock in itself
and a market leader stock. We will discuss the
fundamentals, technicals and business of the stock
and subscribe is important. We are going to talk in
detail about at which level we should buy.
But before that, if you have not subscribed to this channel, then
please
subscribe. If you want to, let's
talk about joining now.
We have gone to the company's website and the
name of the company is ICICI Lombard General
Insurance, that is, except life insurance, all the
business of ICL Group which
comes under Inch Plus, all this is managed by ICICI
Lombard. The segment in which it
works is the car segment, car insurance,
two-wheeler insurance, travel
insurance, health insurance, cyber
business, so many other types of
non-life insurance businesses come here.
ICICI Lombard conducts its operations here
and here also it has a very good
quantity of insurance.  Generally,
people understand that there is good growth in life insurance, but
in the non-life sector, American general insurance is
also seeing very good growth. For the long term,
as literacy increases, the
demand for health insurance will
increase. People will understand
that it is very important. So,
where will this business go? It will go to the company.
ICICI Lombard
is the market leader in its tractor segment. There is jealousy towards two types of companies.
One is a private company and the other
is a public company, which means PSU
companies. But among private companies,
ICICI Lombard has the highest
market share, so it
shows itself as the market leader in its segment. ICICI Lombard has a
market share of more than 8 percent, due to which
very
good growth is seen in the business where ICICI Lombard conducts business. For example, if there is car
insurance, two-wheeler insurance, or
travel insurance, then people's
disposable income is increasing. You
can see the data of 10 years and 20 years in this, and
we see the per capita income increasing.  It has just
started in India,
income has just started, so as the
disposable income increases, then the demand for cars,
two-wheelers for travelling will
increase, people's hobbies will increase, so
for that, inch plus is also necessary, so
ICICI Lombard Market, it can be
seen to be making very good profits,
I am not talking about 12 years, let me
talk about the benefits of the coming 10 years, 20 years
and if you want to get more information about the company,
what are your lines, all the plans
are visible here,
if you want to get information in the interest two-wheeler stress, then you
can think about visiting the website, if we
talk about the stock, then it is doing straight
1414, which
is available on one person's correction, the huge
market phase of 6400, so there is not much focus on difference, there is
more focus on growth, the
peer pressure of the industry is 34.80 kw, which
is above f-35, price regression  If it is
seen above 11:00 then you and the
stock appear to be trading at a premium valuation
but the reason for this is the
performance of the company. The performance of the company is
looking very good. In 2017, the
revenue was 7.5 to 1000, which increased to 12.45 to
1000. Profit is continuously increasing,
increasing from 0.7 to 1.19 and
it is expected that
it will be seen increasing in the coming years. The reason for this is
that ICICI Lombard has
acquired Indian General Insurance, so
its business is also going to come to someone. This is
not a matter of today, it has been a few months,
about which we have discussed in detail,
it will not appear red but as we
give years, then we will see this number repeating, so it is
expanding, the company
was already Mario, but after doing this once, the
market share has increased even more,
so this always
shows a very positive bar for the company. Promoter's
setting  51.8 out of which there
is nothing wrong, this is a good thing. If we talk about FI I have investor
27.1 percent total desires 15.12, then
investment of 5.8 percent is visible. If we
talk about the sales growth of the company, then it
is very good.
Any company can get approval for 5s in one year, the
sales have doubled, the profit has doubled, but
where does it happen consistently, this is very
important, so you
will see sales growth of more than 22% in fiber,
this is the cream due to which the
valuation premium is visible. If we
talk about profit growth, then
in the last five years there has been a profit growth of 70%,
that is why
we are seeing very good growth.
Regarding western dresses,
you will see that for the last 5 years, the profit has been
maintained at above 20%, this is a very
positive thing. If we talk about the profit, then the
return and capital end is
above 126, here also the maximum return  If we see rebellious times,
this is the reason why valuations are expensive here. We
can see all this. We have
reached the chart of ICICI Lombard, where we see
that the stock is currently showing solid momentum. It
fell from 100 only,
then formed a dam, but then
started again, we see it in celebration and
in the face of decline. Felt is seen
coming down, it is seen straightening around its two remedies'
moving average.
Talking about indicators, and this number is 498, which has been seen
comparatively wary.
Talking about MS Word, the money minded
is 37.4, which seems to be very high.
If it goes below this level, then
you will see a more negative overall situation.
Talking about remedies, currently the
police effect is still there, but
according to the situation visible on the chart, the
stars can appear even more
bound at any time. Bollinger
Talking about the base, the
stock is approaching the lower bank of the Bollinger Bands. The
level of 11384 is the medium, the level of 1437 is the
upper band and the level of 1490 is the upper band.
Talking about the quote point, the level
of 11448 is labeled Happy Birthday Resistance. If we
talk about the support below the 151 level, then the first plate of 1362 is
showing support. Talking about the long-term performance of the company, it is
not a very old listed company,
but you will see that after listing, the
stock has shown good returns. The
stock was listed in the end of 2017
and a great rise was seen in the stock. The
stock went up to 660 and reached 1300,
but after that there was a good
correction because the market
saw a crush and again the growth story continued. We saw the
Israel stock
exceed 120 and currently
we see it entering the celebration again,
whereas there has been a decline in the stock, so the
twenty stage  Moving averages provide
important support, and
we see the uptrend continuing.
Currently, the Twenty20 moving
average is above the current market price,
meaning it's trading in the support zone. Therefore, we see
very good
investment opportunities.
I still remember when it reached
around 100, and we'll
see a decline thereafter.
Tensions were rising before the budget, so
we bought around 100. We
also booked profits at 15 sugar levels for short-term investments. However, those
who have already mixed their pockets
can consider investing in this stock even now. It's a good stock. The fundamentals have been
discussed. The returns and research are very
good. The sales growth and profit
growth are also very good. It's a
market leader in the segment it operates in,
so it's a
very good candidate for the long term. True
long-term investors
prefer minimal volatility.
ICICI  Something similar is happening in Lombard, you
will see that you generally do not see much movement in the stock, the
stock trades in the same range for months, after that it
shifts to a direct range, you will
see that similar
trends are seen in the first, there is more
trading volume here, Taurus is a
very liquid sign, we will not do this service
but you do not have the skill here, you can
cancel it like a great Shah for the long term, you can add it to your portfolio
and at the same time if you
want to get your problems reviewed then
I have given its link in the description box, so
if you like the video then
like, share, comment,
subscribe, motivate me,
thank you, stay posted here